I'm cold!
My butt hurts!
Go-tour cherry blossom trip
in Hokkaido
I'm Honoo Tamura of Sakurazaka46
I'm from Yamazaki prefecture.
I'm in New Chitose Airport.
I'm at New Chitose Airport.
Yay!
I'm going to Sapporo from here.
I'm going to Sapporo to appear in various media
I'm going to have a lot of media appearances, eat delicious food, etc.
It's going to be great!
Let's go snowboarding!
I want to dive!
You're early.
The divers are early.
I'm looking forward to it.
How's it going?
It's great.
Wow.
Run, Tenchan.
Go run!
Oh, man.
First time playing in the snow
It's so soft.
Oh, man.
It's fun. It's really fun.
I've been so excited all day.
I always am today.
White and beautiful.
I've had a lot of fun, and I'm really going to enjoy myself today.
Let's see what we can eat!
I'm heading to HTV now.
I'm going to go to HTV now.
I'm so glad that we could come to see you this time.
I'm so happy that we were able to come and see you this time!
Yes, I wanted to be there the most.
Let's go to Hokkaido!
I'll do my best!
Part-time job!
There!
Nice to meet you!
We've arrived!
Let's get dressed.
Ready!
Ta-da!
I'm dressed now!
I'm going to answer a question or two for Mr. HTV.
Let's do our best!
Let's have fun!
I'm off!
I'm going to appear on "Ichi Q&A!
I've been invited to appear on "Ichi Q&A!
It's over, the recording! Thank you very much!
Backstage.
Yes, what a surprise!
We found something, didn't we?
Ta-da! I'm so happy!
Yay!
We've prepared a lot of Hokkaido's specialties for you.
Eat up, Ten-chan!
Let's eat!
Tarako Butter
I'll have the cod roe butter
Bon appétit!
Oh! Amazing!
Tarako!
I'm so happy!
This looks delicious.
Do you want some white peach chocolate with that?
Yes, I do.
Yum.
Lori's the best.
Nice ride.
Next we're going to Air Gesa.
It's my first time in the snow. First time in my life.
How does it feel?
Like in a movie, no kidding.
When we came here, we saw the snow, and we were like, "Airco, this is not a set.
Yay!
I just finished recording and performing live on the radio. I was really happy.
And I was so happy to feel everyone's love.
I'm going to go to a place called Moerenuma Park.
I heard it's really famous. Playing in the snow...
I want to play in the snow.
I want to go there soon.
I'm going to play in the snow.
A Mimio.
I've already prepared a cute little Mimio.
For this trip.
It's cute.
It looks good on you.
Do we all look good? We do.
What do you think?
We're here.
We're here, but?
We're here.I got here.
It was snowy.
It's amazing.
Do you think it'll show?
Wow! Snow!
It's snowing.
Ready?
Wow!
Snow!
Look!
It looks like a face!
Ta-da!
Oh, my God!
Oh, no!
Laughs.
Oh!
Laughing.
I'm so happy!
Wow!
That's great!
Yes!
This is the Cherry Blossom Forest, isn't it?
It's a famous place for cherry blossoms. It seems to be a famous place.
In spring, they will be in full bloom.
But now it is covered with snow!
It seems that the best time to see the cherry blossoms is during Golden Week.
I hope you will come to see the cherry blossoms during Golden Week!
Oh no! I'm about to go on live TV...
Oh, I'm dead!
Not there at all!
Oh, he's dead!
Uh, who are you?
Your dumplings are frozen.
The dumplings on the train are frozen.
What? That's not what I was expecting.
I was like, "Oh, my God!
Meringue...
This is the worst!
It was like a first love vlog on the slopes.
It's a little bit emasculating...
I didn't want to take a cute picture...
Oh no! I almost cried!
It was fun, but so much fun.
It was so much fun. Congratulations!
I don't think I've ever done anything like that. There's no way I'm dashing like that, yesterday.
See you on live TV.
I'll do my best!
Seino! Nice to meet you!
It's really the closest I've ever been to Hokkaido.
I've never seen snow before.
Really?
I've played in all kinds of snow.
Snow.
We've arrived at our final destination.
And now I'd like to show you something.
Ready!
Ta-da!
Scraddie!
Here we are at Lamma-chan!
I'm so happy!
Looks delicious!
Vegetables, I can't decide!
Weapons. What weapons?
It says "weapon" on it.
It's for the house.
Yum!
Cheese and rice!
It's too good!
The one Somo-chan ordered.
Looks delicious!
I'll have chicken.
The cheese is amazing!
Bon appétit!
There's cheese!
There you go.
Is it good?
Yes, it is.
Oh, man, I can't narrow it down to just one.
It's delicious.
If we didn't do these activities.
I'd never have met the things.
Yeah.
It makes me happy.
I don't know.
I feel like I've met Sen-chan
You're kidding.
It's delicious.
You mean it's good?
That's what it means.
Somo-chan!
Somo-chan.
Isn't this your first time?
Here.
I'm just going to check.
Kimochan, Makotochan...SomochanMakoto-chan
Somo-chan
Somo-chan on the way
It's always interesting, isn't it?
It's really great!
Who doesn't laugh when you say that?
Ori-Chun
Me... me... me...
An unknown partner is terrible!
What?
I said a lot of things.
In English now.
Briefly.
Good.
Be concise.
I like it.
Please go towards the store.
Thank you for the food.
It was delicious.
I'm full.
I'm so satisfied.
Thank you very much.
You're not going to build a snowman? What?
The snowman is too soft.
Is it as soft as a rice ball?
You mean? Yeah, fluffy.
Do you have it? Do you have it?
I don't think so. I don't think so.
I've been thinking it's the size of a snowman, but that's all I've been thinking about.
Here it is! It's a snowman!
Go to Sakura Trip in Hokkaido is over.
Thank you for your hard work. It was a lot of fun.
The "Go to Cherry Blossom Trip" was a lot of fun.
I think we were able to deliver all the songs included in the album to people in various places.
I think it was a very meaningful trip.
Yes, I hope you will enjoy listening to the songs with Sakura-ka during the cherry blossom season, and I hope you all enjoy the trip.
I hope that you will also visit Hokkaido.
I hope we can come back to Hokkaido again.
Yes, I'll do my best.
I'll do my best. Thank you very much.
Hokkaido is...
Hokkaido.